Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Staff correspondence, 1904-1952; Series 1; 17 microfilm reels
  - Miscellaneous, ante 1910, 1938-1941, 1947, 1950-1951, n.d; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 47)
  - Miller, Murray W., 1946; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 48)
  - Miller, Murray W., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 49)
    Note in original finding aid reads "(No Corres.)"
  - Miller, Murray W., 1948-1950; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 50)
  - Miller, Murray W., 1951; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 51)
  - Miller, Murray W., 1952; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 52)
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 53)
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1945; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 54)
    Note in original finding aid reads "(No Correspondence)"
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1946-1947; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 55)
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1948-1949; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 56)
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1950; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 57)
  - Mohn, Einar 0., 1951; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 58)
  - Morrissey, Nicholas, 1947; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 59)
  - Morrissey, Nicholas, 1948; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 60)
  - Morrissey, Nicholas, 1949-1950; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 61)
  - Morrissey, Nicholas, 1951; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 62)
  - Morrissey, Nicholas, 1952; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 63)
  - Mullin, E. J., 1907; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 64)
  - Mullin, E. J., 1908; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 65)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1913; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 66)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 67)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 68)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 69)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 70)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 71)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 72)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 73)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1921; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 74)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1922; Series 1 (Reel 14, Segment 75)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1923; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 1)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1924; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 2)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1925; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 3)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1926; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 4)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1927; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 5)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1928; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 6)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1929; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 7)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1930; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 8)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1931; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 9)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1932; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 10)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1933; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 11)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1934; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 12)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1935; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 13)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1936; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 14)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 15)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 16)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 17)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 18)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1941; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 19)
  - Murphy, Daniel J., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 20)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1936; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 21)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 22)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 23)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 24)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 25)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1941; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 26)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1942; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 27)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1943; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 28)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 29)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1945; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 30)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1946; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 31)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1947-1948; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 32)
  - Murphy, Edward F., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 15, Segment 33)
  - Murrin, Gale F., 1948; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 1)
  - Murrin, Gale F., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 2)
  - Murrin, Gale F., 1950; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 3)
  - Murrin, Gale F., 1951; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 4)
  - Murrin, Norman C., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 5)
  - Murrin, Norman C., 1946; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 6)
  - National Conference, 1944 September 23; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 7)
  - Neal, Thomas T., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 8)
  - Neal, Thomas T., 1942; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 9)
  - Neal, Thomas T., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 10)
  - Niemeier, William, 1921-1923; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 11)
  - O'Brien, John J., 1936-1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 12)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1928-1929; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 13)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1930; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 14)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1931; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 15)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1932; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 16)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1933; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 17)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1934; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 18)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1935; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 19)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1936; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 20)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 21)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 22)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 23)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 24)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1942; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 25)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 26)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1945-1946; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 27)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1947-1948; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 28)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 29)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1950; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 30)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1951; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 31)
  - O'Brien, Thomas P., 1952; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 32)
  - O'Neal, A. E., 1945; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 33)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1907; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 34)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1908; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 35)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1909; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 36)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1910; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 37)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1911; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 38)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1912; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 39)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1913; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 40)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1914; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 41)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1915; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 42)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1916; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 43)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1917; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 44)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1918; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 45)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1919; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 46)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1920; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 47)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1921; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 48)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1922; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 49)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1923; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 50)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1924; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 51)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1925-1926; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 52)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1927; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 53)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1928; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 54)
    Note in original finding aid reads "(No Corresp.)"
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1929-1930 (No Corresp.); Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 55)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1931; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 56)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1932; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 57)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1933; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 58)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1934; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 59)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1935; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 60)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1936; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 61)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1937; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 62)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1938; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 63)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1939; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 64)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 65)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1941; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 66)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1942; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 67)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1943; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 68)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1944-1945; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 69)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1946; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 70)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1947; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 71)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1948; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 72)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1949; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 73)
  - O'Neil, Mary, 1950; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 74)
  - Owner-Operators, 1951; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 75)
  - Owner-Operators-Gas Stations, 1943, 1945; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 76)
  - Pendergast, Charles M., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 77)
  - Pendergast, Charles M., 1948; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 78)
  - Pendergast, Charles M., 1949-1951; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 79)
  - Pendergast, Charles M., 1952; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 80)
  - Picago, John S., 1937; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 81)
  - Picago, John S., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 82)
  - Picago, John S., 1939; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 83)
  - Picago, John S., 1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 84)
  - Picago, John S., 1943; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 85)
  - Picago, John S., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 86)
  - Picago, John S., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 87)
  - Policy - International, 1905-1907; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 88)
  - Policy - Office Employees, 1947-1949; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 89)
  - Politics, 1942-1952; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 90)
  - Prohl, Frank, 1938; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 91)
  - Prohl, Frank, 1939; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 92)
  - Prohl, Frank, 1940; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 93)
  - Prohl, Frank, 1943-1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 94)
  - Prohl, Frank, 1947; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 95)
  - Reed, A. J., 1911; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 96)
  - Reed, A. J., 1912; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 97)
  - Reed, A. J., 1913; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 98)
  - Reed, A. J., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 99)
  - Reed, A. J., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 100)
  - Reed, A. J., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 101)
  - Reed, A. J., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 102)
  - Reed, A. J., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 103)
  - Reed, A. J., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 104)
  - Reed, A. J., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 105)
  - Ruehl, James R., 1943-1944; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 106)
  - Ruehl, James R., 1945-1946; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 107)
  - Ruehl, James R., 1947-1948; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 108)
  - Ruehl, James R., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 109)
    Note in original finding aid reads "(no correspondence)"
  - Ruehl, James R., 1950; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 110)
  - Ruehl, James R., 1951-1952; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 111)
  - St. Clair, A. L., 1909; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 112)
  - St. Clair, A. L., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 113)
  - Shea, Cornelius P., 1904; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 114)
  - Shea, Cornelius P., 1905; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 115)
  - Shea, Cornelius P., 1909; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 116)
  - Showier, Birt, 1919; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 117)
  - Showier, Birt, 1920; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 118)
  - Silva, Antoine, 1907; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 119)
  - Silva, Antoine, 1908; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 120)
  - Silva, Antoine, 1909; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 121)
  - Silva, Antoine, 1910; Series 1 (Reel 16, Segment 122)
  - Steelhaulers, 1949-1952; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 1)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1946; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 2)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1947; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 3)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1948; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 4)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1949; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 5)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1950; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 6)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1951; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 7)
  - Thirion, Harold, 1952; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 8)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Administrative Assistant to the President, 1940; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 9)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Personal, 1917-1932; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 10)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Personal, 1933-1936; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 11)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Personal, 1937-1951; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 12)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Possible appointment to the Senate, 1944; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 13)
  - Tobin, Daniel J. - Speeches and Clippings, 1928-1945; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 14)
  - Tobin, Frank L., 1942-1943; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 15)
  - Tobin, Frank L., 1944-1949, 1950; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 16)
  - Tobin, Frank L., 1951; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 17)
  - Tobin, Frank L., 1952; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 18)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1938; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 19)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1939-1940; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 20)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1941-1942; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 21)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1943; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 22)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 23)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1945; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 24)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1946; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 25)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 26)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1948; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 27)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 28)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1950-1951; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 29)
  - Tobin, Fred A., 1952; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 30)
  - Truck Check, 1949-1952; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 31)
  - Veterans, 1944-1946; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 32)
  - Weizenecker, G. F., 1948-1949; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 33)
  - Welch, James A., 1910; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 34)
  - Welch, James A., 1911; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 35)
  - Welch, James A., 1912; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 36)
  - Welch, James A., 1913; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 37)
  - Welch, James A., 1914; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 38)
  - Welch, James A., 1915; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 39)
  - Welch, James A., 1916; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 40)
  - Welch, James A., 1917; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 41)
  - Welch, James A., 1918; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 42)
  - Welch, James A., 1919; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 43)
  - Welch, James A., 1920; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 44)
  - Wooddall, R. F., 1944; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 45)
  - Wooddall, R. F., 1947; Series 1 (Reel 17, Folder 46)
  - Zolg, H. J., 1949; Series 1 (Reel 17, Segment 47)
- Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, 1907-1952; Series 2; 47 microfilm reels
  This series consists of exchanges between the executive office and the local unions, joint councils, conferences, and trade divisions affiliated with the I.B.T.
  Organized into four subseries: Local unions correspondence, Joint Council correspondence, Area and state conferences correspondence, and Trade Divisions correspondence.
  - Local unions correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1
    The local union is the basic unit of I.B.T. organization. These files are those of the I.B.T. President's office and contain exchanges of Tobin and his representatives with local union officers, business agents, and members; the joint councils and occasionally the conferences to which the locals belong; and the I.B.T. general organizers, lawyers, and Washington representatives on subjects concerning the locals. Organizing drives, contract negotiations, strikes, cases before the National Labor Relations Board and the Wage Stabilization Board, bylaws, elections, members' complaints and problems, and many other topics are discussed. The files date mainly during the 1940 's and vary in degree of completeness.
    Arranged numerically by local number and chronological thereunder
    - All locals, 1907, 1935, 1943-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 1)
    - Local #2, Butte, Montana, 1942, 1944, 1947, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 2)
    - Local #3, Collinsville, Illinois, 1933, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 3)
    - Local #6, Grand Junction, Colorado, 1943, 1945, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 4)
    - Local #6, St. Louis, Missouri, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 5)
    - Local #7, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1937, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 6)
    - Local #8, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 7)
    - Local #10, Duquoin, Illinois, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 8)
    - Local #11, Evansville, Indiana, 1941, 1945-1946, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 9)
    - Local #13, Denver, Colorado, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 10)
    - Local #17, Denver, Colorado, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 11)
    - Local #18, Bloomington, Illinois, 19l*7-l°l*8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 12)
    - Local #20, Toledo, Ohio, 1914, 1940, 19l*6; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 13)
    - Local #21, Center, Missouri, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 14)
    - Local #22, Toledo, Ohio, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 15)
    - Local #24, Akron, Ohio, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 16)
    - Local #25, Boston, Massachusetts, 1907, 1938-1943, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 17)
    - Local #26, Danville, Illinois, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 18)
    - Local #28, Springfield, Missouri, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 19)
    - Local #29, Massillon, Ohio, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 20)
    - Local #32, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 21)
    - Local #32, Duluth, Minnesota, 1942, 1946, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 22)
    - Local #33, Washington, D.C., 1942, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 23)
    - Local #36, San Diego, California, 1918; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 24)
    - Local #38, Everett, Washington, 1944, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 25)
    - Local #39, Hillsboro, Illinois, 1925; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 26)
    - Local #39, Buffalo, New York, 1942, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 27)
    - Local #40, Mansfield, Ohio, 1943, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 28)
    - Local #41, Kansas City, Missouri, 1941, 1945, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 29)
    - Local #42, Lynn, Massachusetts, 1946-1948, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 30)
    - Local #43, Racine, Wisconsin, 1943, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 31)
    - Local #44, Seattle, Washington, 1936, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 32)
    - Local #45, Great Falls, Montana, 1916, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 33)
    - Local #47, Fort Worth, Texas, 1943-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 34)
    - Local #48, Alton, Illinois, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 35)
    - Local #49, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1943, 1945, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 36)
    - Local #50, Belleville, Illinois, 1920, 1922-1925, 1947, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 37)
    - Local #51, Detroit, Michigan, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 38)
    - Local #52, Cleveland, Ohio, 1942, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 39)
    - Local #53, Bozeman, Montana, 1944, 1947, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 40)
    - Local #54, Hutchinson, Kansas, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 41)
    - Local #55, Kingsport, Tennessee, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 42)
    - Local #56, Sheboygan, Wisconsin, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 43)
    - Local #58, Longview, Washington, 1946, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 44)
    - Local #59, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1911; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 45)
    - Local #59, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 46)
    - Local #61, Granite City, Illinois, 1920-1923, 1943-1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 47)
    - skipped, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 48)
    - Local #64, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1919- 1920; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 49)
    - Local #65, Ithaca, New York, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 50)
    - Local #67, Washington, D. C., 1919, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 51)
    - Local #69, Centralia, Illinois, 1922, 1941,, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 52)
    - Local #70, Alameda County, California, 1933, 1946-1947, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 53)
    - Local #71, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1944-1945, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 54)
    - Local #72, Des Moines, Iowa, 1946, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 55)
    - Local #73, Clinton, Indiana, 1943, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 56)
    - Local #75, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1938, 1944, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 57)
    - Local #76, Pana, Illinois, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 58)
    - Local #78, Alameda County, California, 1943, 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 59)
    - Local #79, Tampa, Florida, 1943, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 60)
    - Local #80, Quincy, Illinois, 1947, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 61)
    - Local #82, Boston, Massachusetts, 1941, 1943-1944, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 62)
    - Local #84, Edwardsville, Illinois, 1945, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 63)
    - Local #85, San Francisco, California, 1908, 1943, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 64)
    - Local #87, Bakersfield, California, 1947, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 65)
    - Local #88, Ashland, Kentucky, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 66)
    - Local #89, Louisville, Kentucky, 1943, 1945- 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 67)
    - Local #90, Des Moines, Iowa, 1941, 1943, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 68)
    - Local #91, Cairo, Illinois, 1941, 1943- 1946, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 69)
    - Local #92, Canton, Illinois, 1944, 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 70)
    - Local #93, Los Angeles, California, 1937, 1942, 1948,, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 71)
    - Local #94, Tulare & Kings County,Calif., 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 72)
    - Local #95, Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1941, 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 73)
    - Local #96, Alameda & Contra Costa Counties, California, 1945, 1947- -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 74)
    - Local #98, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 75)
    - Local #100, Cincinnatit Ohio, 1942-1943, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 76)
    - Local #102, Taylorville, Illinois, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 77)
    - Local #103, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1944, 1950, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 78)
    - Local #104, Phoenix, Arizona, 1947, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 79)
    - Local #105, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1943, 1946- 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 80)
    - Local #106, Pottsville, Pennsylvania, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 81)
    - Local #107, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1936, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 82)
    - Local #110, Johnstown, Pennsylvania, 1936, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 83)
    - Local #113, Houston, Texas, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 84)
    - Local #113, Canton, Ohio, 1946, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 85)
    - Local #114, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1944, 1947, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 86)
    - Local #116, Fargo, North Dakota, 1944, 1947, 1950- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 87)
    - Local #117, Seattle, Washington, 1936, 1940- 1941, 1947-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 18, Segment 88)